allbestapps.net 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy - AllBestApps

When you use AllBestApps or create an account on AllBestApps, you provide AllBestApps with data enabling to identify you personally. The herein Policy explains how the data collected by AllBestApps is processed. 

This Policy does not apply to information collected by third party websites linked to or accessible from AllBestApps, which is subject to the privacy policies of these websites.

The AllBestApps website has been registered to the French data protection authority (CNIL) under number 2002548.

In accordance with Article 34 of the law no. 78-17 of 6th January 1978 regarding computing, files and freedom, you have the right to access, modify, rectify and delete any data that concerns you. You can exercise this right by sending us a message using our contact form or by simple mail to our registered office. 

## Data collection

AllBestApps collects personal data when an account is created and when the Website is used. AllBestApps also collects data on other websites. 

### Data you provide us with

When creating a AllBestApps Account, we remind you that it is important that you retain your login and your password and you keep this information secret. 

If you have a AllBestApps Account, you benefit from an online access to most of your personal data. Therefore you can modify the data associated to your Account or delete your Account via your Personal Space at any time.

### Data collected when you use our services

The Website reserves the right, for the needs of the services provided, to place “cookies” in your computer and access them. You can choose not to accept saving “cookies” by adjusting your browser settings. 

In order to comply with legal and regulatory obligations, to avoid all abusive uses of the Website and its services, or to perform statistical analysis, navigation data and IP addresses can be gathered as well. 

### Data collected on other services

AllBestApps may collect and display data about you that is publicly available on other websites. 

We access such data in accordance with the data access policies of the websites and applicable user specific privacy settings. 

If you do not want your personal data to be collected or published by AllBestApps, you may adjust the account privacy settings of your account with your service provider in order to prevent your information from being publicly accessed.

## Use of data

AllBestApps uses this data for several purposes:

\- to operate and optimize the Website and its services;

\- to customize advertising content posted on the Website;

\- to answer users' requests about some services. 

## Links to other websites

The Website contains links to other websites. 

AllBestApps is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other websites. 

When navigating to another website, the user should acknowledge the privacy policy stated on the recipient website. 

Only this Privacy Policy governs data collected on the AllBestApps Website.
